so how do you actually sell $10,000 per
month consistently of online courses
well the truth is most people can't
because they've never been taught the
skills and most of what they know how to
do or have been taught simply doesn't
work I'm going to show you what is
working and what has worked for the last
21 years I've dedicated my entire life
and career to helping the top mentors
trainers and coaches scale their
businesses we built multiple businesses
in the online coaching and digital
course space as well as selling CD DVD
products seminars and Retreats
businesses that have made over 10 and
even $20 million per year in this space
and I love helping people that are just
starting out if you're just starting out
how to know what the steps are to take
by the end of this video you are going
to have a blueprint that you can use to
be able to build and successfully sell
courses that are going to be able to pay
you full-time online okay now what are
the first steps of actually doing this
well the first step is you got to figure
out what you're actually going to make a
course on what's marketable what are the
topics what Niche right everybody says
you have to find a niche I'll tell you
this we have to think of a niche not as
a what but as a who and what you want is
you want these to be your
true people okay what is the difference
between true people well here's the
difference true people or
followers right a follower is it's it's
very simple you go on a platform like
Instagram or Facebook somebody presses a
little red button follow or subscribe on
YouTube which by the way if you're
watching this click the Subscribe
button but that's not really what's
going to build a business you need to
figure out how to create connection with
true people that want to go deep with
you that want to do life with you that
they want to be mentored by you and they
want you to show them what you know that
they don't okay now here's the cool part
about this whatever you know today you
can learn new stuff you can learn new
skills you're not stuck with just what
you know how to do today and I think
that that's actually a beautiful thing I
would not recommend however just simply
selling a course about something that
you learned last week right or stuff
that you maybe watched five YouTube
videos on and then you're like okay I'm
going to teach that same thing but I'm
going to charge $1,000 for it people can
see through that okay and we live in a
world today especially with artificial
intelligence which is coming after the
jobs of a lot of creators online right
now that people want more depth more
authenticity they don't want things to
be robotic or what they can already find
online okay so what we have to do is we
have to dive deeper into figuring out
who these people are and generally
that's going to be maybe only five to
15% of your followers so I may have
2,000 people that follow me on a YouTube
channel but who I'm really concerned
about
mostly what's what's uh 15% of of 2,000
that's 300 people so who are the 300
people that subscribe to my channel and
you're probably one of them who's
watching this that really truly is going
to do one of two things you're going to
actually follow what I teach you're
going to actually implement it you're
not just gathering information because
it makes you feel good and can I tell
you this you don't want people that are
just information gatherers you want
action takers people who are going to
put you to the test prove you and see if
what you say works and then they're
going to report back with the results to
you that's what we have we have people
that they apply exactly what I teach on
this channel and they come back to me
and share Jeremiah I made $25,000 this
month like my client dawn has done or or
I made $115,000 this month like Duke did
or like like um Judy did over $37,000
just applying one strategy that she
learned from one of our trainings and so
this this I don't say that to brag or or
to say hey look all these amazing people
are doing this what I want to say is
that you want that you want people that
are actually going to take what you
teach what you're putting in your course
what's actually on your cont content and
they are going to apply it one of the
biggest issues though however is that
people are just trying to look and
appear professional okay you might see
me up here and I can tell you listen to
this compared to a lot of competitors
that I might have in the space I have a
a pretty Bare Bones basic setup it's
some of my favorite things a lot of
video game stuff some of my favorite
books got a got a comic book t-shirt on
and a and a whiteboard right here but
like beyond that like I don't have fancy
cameras it's a $0 camera that I got off
of
Amazon it's attached to my laptop it's a
it's a $100 microphone right here on my
desk I got a $30 light over here okay so
I keep it really really simple when it
comes to the equipment and I've always
done that for years because what matters
is focusing more on the connection that
I can make with people if I can connect
with
you and I can show you that something is
possible and I can walk you through the
process that's way more important to me
than looking like I got it all together
like I got it all figured out and I
guarantee you that if you watch some of
my content you're going to see that
that's the case that again if you're
watching my stuff and all you're doing
is judging the sound quality and the
video quality maybe you
are I'm probably not a good fit to work
with and you're probably not my true
people I I've actually figured this out
actually by the way I know that you're
not I I say probably but the truth is I
know that you're not because I don't
work with people that are like that I
don't work with people that are so
stringently perfectionistic that
everything needs to be so perfect or
it's unacceptable okay and so if that's
you I would encourage you to maybe grow
in that area past and move Beyond
perfectionism and this is one of the
number one things that actually stops
people from being successful when it
comes to creating a coar business is
their perfectionism they need it to be
so perfect that they don't actually put
anything out there I was just watching a
presentation from the CEO of patreon and
he was talking about this saying that
now we live in a different type of
Creator economy where you don't always
know what's going to hit with content
especially in the beginning and so it's
better to try out different things and
see who your true people are I actually
got this concept right here of true
people versus followers from watching
his video that he did from South by
Southwest here this year it really
resonated with me I was like that's it
that's exactly it who are are my people
who is my tribe who are the ones that I
want to do life with that I could go out
to dinner with and say this is literally
like the most favorite people that I
have in the world next to my wife and
son that's who I want to engage with
that's who I want more of watching my
content and that's who actually buys the
courses coaching and mentorship that we
offer okay and so with that you want to
keep that in mind it's not about you
creating something that's going to be
Mass Market it's about finding maybe 50
to 100 people that need a problem solve
that you know how to solve now you might
be listening to this right now saying
Jeremiah I don't have anything I can
solve problems for people with I I I I
beg to differ and I disagree with that
and this is a this is a belief that I
would encourage you to challenge and
look at in one
step take a look at your life 15 years
ago just think about it maybe you
haven't thought about it in a while
you were probably making some mistakes
in life right but you had certain goals
that you still have today so I want you
to to correlate these things together
and this will help you identify who your
true people are as well as your Niche or
topic is you have yourself 15 years ago
okay and you have
today and the golden thread that goes
between these two is which goals
and
dreams do you have that you have come
closer to today that you were further
away from 15 years ago and what did you
learn over the course of 15 years that
got you closer to these dreams and goals
today by the way you don't need to be at
the Finish
Line you don't need to have a million
dollar
portfolio but maybe you've been grinding
the circuit trying to get a job on
Broadway for 15 years and actually you
have had supporting roles but maybe you
weren't a lead in Hamilton
right but you have some things that you
didn't know 15 years ago that now you
know today that you could pass on to
people that are where you were 15 years
ago and these become your true fans
because what's connected with this your
true followers not just fans but your
true people the ones who are committed
the ones who are actually going to make
an investment the ones who are actually
going to take action with what it is
that you teach you want to find action
takers Risk Takers people that are
willing to do the work they're not
complainers they're not whiners and
they're
teachable and if I can tell you this if
you are somebody who comes into my space
and you work with me and you're a whiner
and you're a complainer and all you got
is a reason why what I teach doesn't
work for you and you think that I'm a
bunch of load of crap or whatever that
is by the way I have people who show up
in my space and say that to me and I
show them the door and I say listen I
mean this with all due respect but
please
let yourself out we don't need that
energy around here okay and they get
offended of course but it's not I
legitimately cannot convince somebody
who is Con is is convicted against
everything that I'm doing that they
should listen to me I don't need to
defend myself I need to as quickly as
possible remove them from my space okay
and this is something that I believe
that if you're looking for
validation if you're looking for
approval from other people you got to
get rid of that behavior that often
comes in whether it be from childhood or
all this type of stuff we're not this
isn't a therapy session here but what I
want to say is that if your main mission
is being seen and heard by other people
you're going to have a really really
hard time building a business in this
space that actually makes you any
money you have to rise above that and
step into a place of
Authority
okay and don't let what anybody says
about you or where you at or where
you've been or your friends or your
family convince you that you're not good
enough today to be able to do
this I know I'm touching on some stuff
right now I know I'm stepping on some
toes right now but can I tell you I
guarantee you that if you take a look at
what our goals and dreams that you have
come closer to today
again your Finish Line might be 50 years
down the
road but maybe you're 15 years along and
you can find somebody who's at year 1 to
five who who wants to accelerate
themselves and save themselves 15 years
worth of headaches by shortening the
timeline with them so what that is is
you take a look at that becomes your
Niche who are those people and then you
want to identify where are they
struggling
Ling what is not working for them to
reach those goals you want to find
people who also have the same goals and
dreams that you
do and this challenges us because
especially if we come at it from an
angle of oh I got to be the one person
who reaches that goal or dream and I
can't help raise up other people behind
me as far as this goes I'm sorry to tell
you but you're not going to be
successful in this space if you can't
help raise up other people to even
surpass you and go beyond where you
are this is why I encourage people my
mission is I want to help a thousand
people become
multi-millionaire coaches mentors course
creators trainers and that's exactly
what we've dedicated ourselves to that's
exactly what I have dedicated my life
and my family and my business
to for the last 21 years and I do
through my client growth accelerator
program this is my coaching program
right here there's a waiting list for it
this isn't an ad for my coaching program
by any means I don't want that to seem
like that's what this
is but I want you to realize that if you
want to create a business that's going
to pay you full-time it has to come from
a real place and you have to connect
with people that are willing to do the
work because they have a big enough
vision the goal and the dream that you
have been able to accomplish and here's
the great part about it is that once you
get 50 to 100 people in your space that
have similar goals and dreams it creates
what is called The Mastermind
effect what is the Mastermind effect if
you've ever read the book Think and Grow
Rich it talks about this Gathering a
group of people that have common goals
interests and desires together that if
you can bring them together
they can accomplish incredible things
beyond what they
imagined together and so this is again
why you have to learn how to celebrate
other people's success be somebody who
raises other people up to go and surpass
you far above and beyond where you are
and that's my mission is if you hear my
success I want you to go far and above
and beyond the success that I have had
with my clients or that I have had in my
own business
businesses and it starts with this it
starts with
identifying who you can help and where
they are at and then taking a look at
two very important
things where are they
struggling and what is their
desire
dream and even if we go to a deeper
level what do they sit up at
night and
fantasize
about what do they think about and even
obsess over that they want to happen for
them and then where is there a crossover
with this this is the people that are
where you might have been 15 10 years
ago what where are they struggling what
do they desire what do they dream of and
then where is there a crossover
with how you have
accomplished this or have helped other
people accomplish this who have also had
a similar struggle then what you do is
you package that into a course or a
training program so you figure out what
is that struggle and what is the
stepbystep process to be able to bring
this together and now this is where it
gets really really really fun is you can
use some very simple artificial
intelligence tools like chat GPT to be
able to type some of this in let's say
that you're somebody who I want
to to help people gain traction on
Broadway to
become an
actor or actress generate me an outline
for an for an
eight module course for this that I can
sell for for for 1,00
$997 and I'll tell you this $2,000 is a
steal compared to the lessons that maybe
you've learned if that's what they're
struggling with as far as this goes the
history of Broadway how to audition
building a strong foundation and so what
this does is this this stimulates your
mind this gives you ideas for what you
could create something around that you
could sell okay as far as this
goes generate
a list of struggles deep desires pain
points and the real deep emotional
reasons someone would buy this course
okay again there might be dealing with
constant rejection lack of opportunities
inconsistent income and you can go into
Ai and type all of this in and it'll
give you ideas for why somebody would
buy this type of stuff
okay generate me a
simple
advertisement letter to promote a course
about the above and that solves these
issues and helps people reach their
dreams okay I misspelled a lot of that
but it it it works just fine transform
your Broadway dream into a reality are
you tired of constant rejection do you
dream of seeing your name in lights but
feel
overwhelmed overcome rejection build
confidence so
again this gives you an idea of
something that you could sell as a
course from one situation that maybe
you've been experiencing maybe you still
are struggling with ideas as far as what
you've been experiencing watch this
generate
me 100 ideas for a course I could sell
niches
topics for
people that are related to my my skills
and you can make a list of skills as far
as this goes right or you can just say
this right here okay and sell for
$1,997 so what you can see right here is
it can actually generate for you ideas
for courses or programs that you could
create as far as this goes so this
starts generating you ideas for this now
here's a kind of a cool thing that you
can say can you ask me some questions
about my career
skills in the last 15 years of my life
to identify where I could make a course
that truly impacts and transforms
people's lives okay so by asking chat
GPT to ask you questions about maybe
your career or things like that look it
you can literally type in what's your
professional background what positions
or roles have you had what achievements
what special skills or certifications
what kind of mentoring who has mentored
you have you mentored others what types
of problems do you solve what kind of
proficiencies do you have you know have
you made any significant career changes
leadership experience networking so you
can literally start to answer some of
these questions and what it'll do and
don't overthink them by the way is it
can start to put a profile together
generate me a sample profile to all of
these questions just brainstorm
something for a random person
or
idea that then we can use as an as an
example fill in the 30 questions above
okay so watch it's going to fill in like
a sample fictitious individual his name
is Alex Thompson his background is
working in the tech industry he's LED
these lead roles this is what he's done
okay here we go so it's filling in like
all this let's just say that this is a
sample person so that we don't have to
actually fill it
in now watch this now take Alex's
answers and generate 100 Niche or
100 Niche or topic ideas that Alex could
make as a course or mentoring program to
sell for
$1,997 okay based on this he could do
any of these types of topics right here
as courses okay now what if he wanted to
take take 10 or 5 to 10 of the best
ideas here and create a community of
people who want to engage with him
deeper what are some ideas for what this
community would be about based on all
the above and his background so again
these are prompts that you could put
into the
AI you can literally pause this video
promp the AI with very similar based on
your life experiences and stuff like
this and it will start to come up with
Community ideas that you could build as
far as this
goes let's combine all of these into one
final community and generate US 20
possible names for this community that
can be marketed online watch it's going
to generate US 20 names for a community
or a mentoring program or a coaching
program based off of this could be
sustainable Tech innovators with Alex it
could be uh you know Green Tech Pioneers
nextg Tech leaders the tech innovators
Alliance AI leadership
Collective um you know uh make it more
about mentoring coaching and the
training that he's doing and make 20
more titles okay so we we'll kind of
we'll steer it more towards the coaching
or mentoring the AI Me mentorship
Network Tech coaching Collective as far
as that goes okay so all of this gives
ideas that if like let let's say that
that was your answers and you can go
fill in answers in here AI can help you
brainstorm a path to take on how to
create a course as well as a community
and listen you could go have some fun
playing around with AI testing out some
of those ideas putting some of those
things together now here's the thing you
might be watching this saying Jeremiah I
I came here to learn how to do a course
what you what's this whole thing about
Community can I tell you something
selling a course by itself is actually
very very difficult to be able to make
the kind of money that you want to make
especially when it's just around one
topic but what becomes far easier to
sell it's way easier to sell it's far
easier to get people to buy
into is when you
offer the
following a membership
community that
combines
courses and listen you could literally
start with like three to four to begin
with that's actually how I started my
community that we have today the
accelerator group when I started the
client growth accelerator I only had
four courses in here and now to this day
we've loaded up I believe there's close
to 50 different courses that we've
actually loaded up in here and and since
there's so many now we've had to we've
organized it into the the key three main
steps that people go through that help
navigate them on what to learn so we
have no topic untaught un un unturned no
stone unturned and our community just
absolutely loves what we have to offer
but to start you don't need 50 courses
like that in fact that's usually
Overkill you usually can start with
three to four and really it can be this
one Flag ship which kind of becomes one
that's like your main overarching
training and then you could have two to
three
supporting uh mini classes so they could
be mini courses with just like two or
three short lessons that break down
certain topics and then you build
something around this that you get
paid monthly on not just a one-time
payment maybe you get paid $47 a month
$97 a month $200 a month for that our
accelerator program at the time of this
recording we're doing it at $200 a month
when people jump in it's a steal for
what people get they also get access
to community okay so you want community
that gives people access to people that
are just like them that are working
through things that they can work with
and come alongside as well as the
support
accountability accountability and
I'm I'm running out of space here but
connection support accountability and
connection so you have some courses up
here that's your training but then you
also have community and you can have
weekly or even bi-weekly or even once a
month support calls with a group of
people and then you provide support you
get to work with them through things you
can you might have a Facebook group or a
patreon or a Discord people have been
using this new platform called school
that's out out there that Alex Heros and
Sam ens have been promoting and so you
put all of this together and this
becomes a th% easier to actually sell to
people because it makes it just makes
sense that being a immersed inside of a
community like this is going to work far
better than just going through a
pre-recorded
course how many of you know that just
going through videos on YouTube can
become very
M you get a little bit of it but like
you really need connection you want to
talk with the people you want to talk
with the person who's actually helping
you one of the things that we offer in
my accelerator program is we help you
build your course we help you create
your sales copy we help you come up with
your marketing we help you dial in and
optimize how you're selling and how
you're getting clients and we work with
you consistently I'm inside of our
Facebook group every single day working
with people to do that and so I tell you
and I urge you to to copy what I'm doing
bring this model in for you and by the
way this is exactly what I Mentor people
on is how to build these types of
coaching mentoring communities to where
you provide some coaching you provide
support you give some Consulting you
have some training in your courses you
have connection with the other members
and you get paid monthly for this and
what happens with
this this creates results for people far
more than anything
else this is far more profitable and you
get to work way less time and hours I
only have to work 10 hours a week to be
able to manage and maintain my community
and so in this you can build a
sustainable business that can pay you 5
10 $25,000
and we've built businesses all the way
up to $20 million a year that are making
over over nearly $2 million a month in
that doing exactly this with just
membership communities okay and so again
I would urge you if you're watching this
right now make sure that you don't
struggle with
this get on the waiting list for my
client growth accelerator program that
when we do open the doors with this you
can work with me and our community to
help create and FastTrack you along this
process what people need is once you
have this
built this is not enough to make money
and I think that that's the part that
people get wrong is they think that once
all of these pieces are put together
that they're going to make
money don't check out here because this
is where most people that they're
watching a video like this they're not
ready to hear this part of what I'm
talking
about you have have to start marketing
what you're doing and you can't drag
your feet or sit on your
feet the the the marketplace is
accelerating as far as ideas are
becoming capitalized on faster than
anybody has ever predicted and with
artificial intelligence now the value of
communities like this is skyrocketing
because people want actual connection
but the value of Simply courses and
information has gone way
down and then what's happening is is
because people are creating programs
like this right now is that you have to
make sure that you get ahead of the
curve and that your idea doesn't
become uh basically replaced by somebody
else who can execute faster this was not
the case 3 years
ago and maybe you're watching this and
maybe you've been wanting to do
something like this for more than 3
years I I have to urge you is that the
longer that you wait the harder it
becomes the longer that you wait to
actually do something to make a decision
about this the harder it becomes and
that becomes actually one of the number
one things that we have to do and that I
also love helping people with is you
have to
decide on a topic or Niche that you're
going to create something around one of
the biggest problems that people have is
they have fomo fear of missing out
you're afraid that if you pick an idea
it's not going to work and so you're
actually letting your fear run and
decide if you're going to show up and
put something out there instead of
experimenting and adopting an
experimentation mindset to create what
we call an alpha release approach where
you create an alpha version of what
you're doing you put it out there you
connect with people maybe you get 50 to
100 people in there and then you refine
it over
time but that alone loan is not going to
make you any money in fact you could do
all of that and
99% of the time the amount of money that
you are going to make is
zero and this is why most people who
come to me they come to me at this stage
where they're making
nothing but they've invested thousands
of hours into trying to create this
thing that they expected to
sell and by the way it doesn't have to
take thousands of hours if you follow
the process that I teach people you can
get the this stuff done in as little as
as as 30 days it's
amazing and you don't have to stay broke
either you can monetize it while you're
doing it many of our clients within the
first 30 to 60 days of launching
something generate 5 to $110,000 a month
and then go beyond that 20,000
35,000 $100,000 a month
$160,000 a month like my client Joshua
Giles did within just six months of
working with us
but it starts by learning one thing how
do you actually sell a program like this
so you have to make a
decision to decide to start somewhere
with something to put yourself out there
and you might need to address the fears
and worries that you might have as to
what are you trying to avoid you cannot
let your fear and worry run your
life you got to put yourself out there
and it might not work out initially but
if you work with somebody like myself if
you work with me my promise is that I
will help make you get results as fast
as humanly
possible because when you apply a proven
system and process you don't have to
wonder is this going to work you just
follow the right way of doing things
okay even then and I just I this is
where I'm different than a lot of other
people that are out there by the way in
this industry okay I'm going to show you
why I'm Different cuz I could stop this
video right there and tell you now go
join my program and stuff like that
first off the doors aren't even even
open there's a waiting list even then
even if you are in my program and you do
all the things there's still a chance
you don't make any kind of money off of
it and and and you might be like well
wait a sec Jeremiah want to well then
what's the value of working with you huh
it's the fact that you have somebody
that can help come back to the drawing
board with you and we can refine it we
can figure out based on a data evidenc
driven
approach to identify what I had
mentioned at the beginning here who are
your true people the reason why if you
did all the right things and you would
still be making zerar has really only
one answer you're not actually reaching
or connecting with your true people
because once you find and identify who
those true people are and you create an
offer that connects directly with where
they are to build a
community it becomes irresistible to
them to become a client of yours to work
with you because it connects
energetically with everything that they
have been hoping and praying for so
here's what you got to do you have to
create marketing campaigns and this is
the part that most course creators and
coaches and mentors struggle with and
that's where I have been an expert for
the last 21 years a self-proclaimed
expert sure I I say that but I've been
doing this successfully for 21 years
I've had a I I I'm not the only one who
calls myself that as well
okay I can walk you through the process
but you have to take action and start
marketing attracting the people to you
that are actually going to take action
and then selling to those people and
that's the part that becomes hard that's
the part that will challenge a lot of
your belief systems about yourself
because you are essentially selling your
essence to people you are selling
something that you have poured your
heart and soul into your baby and you're
inviting people to join you and here's
what ends up happening is we end up
becoming worried about critiques from
other people are they going to like it
are they going to be disappointed is it
going to work for everybody I'll tell
you this you have to learn to let go of
that and just have full excitement and
faith and belief and put it out there I
see people all the time they don't put
anything out there because they need
certainty to know that it's going to
work and it's going to produce
results the only certain thing is this
that I know is that if you stick with a
proven process things start to work for
you when you work with somebody that has
been doing this for as long as I have
whether it be me be me or somebody else
and you start to actually do the work
work and you don't make excuses and you
don't complain and you say you know what
maybe just maybe I might need to change
how I'm looking at this change the
perspective and then you start to go to
work and you start to apply it what ends
up happening is you start to get your
first five
sales and your next five sales and you
start having people registering with you
and becoming clients of yours and now
you're making connection with your true
people and then you start scaling this
to where you might get 50 100 300 people
you can literally have a sixf figure
business with 100
people 100 people paying you $83 a month
80 bucks a month is over $100,000 a
year I know the math is off in the 80
bucks but
yes why are you what are you waiting for
and I think and I got to ask you that
and that's what I want to close this
with I want you to challenge yourself on
that one
what are you waiting
for what are you expecting to happen
well I'm just going to lay the
foundations I'm going to wait till I
feel ready I'm going to wait till
Everything feels right and I got peace
in my heart about it can I tell you this
a lot of this stuff is going to
challenge what feels normal for you and
in the beginning you might have to take
action and do it scared and you might
have to take a risk and you might have
to do something that you've never done
before put yourself out there without
knowing how it's going to turn out
most every single person who has ever
been successful in this space has had to
do that the reason why people are not
successful is they are not willing to
put themselves out there without
certainty of what's going to happen and
those who are the most successful they
are willing to take imperfect
action they're will they're willing to
try things out just to see what works
and then optimize it and work with a
mentor and a coach to help bring things
to
life I believe you can do that that but
it's going to take challenging how
you've always done things and how you're
looking at the possibilities that you
are
creating I'd love to work with you
through this process as well if you
continue following my YouTube channel
right here if you subscribe we're going
to be creating new videos to help you
through this process if I've shared
something here today and maybe it's
challenged something in you leave me a
comment below and let me know a number
one what was it that had challenging you
what did you think about it but number
two
what other videos would you like to see
us create on this channel and as well
then join the waiting list for the
accelerator when we open the doors to
that for enrollment next which isn't
going to be anytime soon necessarily but
when we do I'd love to have you in there
to try it out to see if it's a good fit
for you all right so thank you for
watching this and I'll see you on our
next video we'll talk soon